



 

   //Questions array

   let questions = [

    {

         number:1,

         question: "Nigerian English has been brought about by the __",

         answer : "Multiplicity of languages",

         options : [

                          "Defects in education system",

                          "Government corruption",

                          "Multiplicity of languages",

                          "Neocolonialism"

                        ]

    

    },

    {

         number:2,

         question: "Who referred to Nigerian English as a misnomer",

         answer : "Fodeh Baldeh",

         options : [

                          "William Wordsworth",

                          "John Keats",

                          "Fodeh Baldeh",

                          "Lord Tennyson"  

                          ]

    

    },

    {

         number:3,

         question: "These factors necessary errors in the use of English except",

         answer : "Multiplicity of languages",

         options : [

                          "Multiplicity of languages",

                          "Problem of orthography",

                          "Mother tongue interference",

                          "Problem of borrowed words"  

                          ]

    

    },

    {

         number:4,

         question: "I am not hearing you‚Äù the error here is caused by",

         answer : "Mother tongue interference",

         options : [

                          "Multiplicity of languages",

                          "Problem of orthography",

                          "Mother tongue interference",

                          "Problem of borrowed words"  

                          ]

    

    },

    {

         number:5,

         question: "They entered into a convenant . The error here is necessitated by",

         answer : "Problem of orthography",

         options : [

                          "Multiplicity of languages",

                          "Problem of orthography",

                          "Mother tongue interference",

                          "Problem of borrowed words"  

                          ]

    

    },

    {

         number:6,

         question: "Sound system or structure is also known as",

         answer : "Orthography",

         options : [

                          "Syntax",

                          "Morphology",

                          "Orthography",

                          "Phonology"  

                          ]

    

    },

    {

         number:7,

         question: "_&_ critically considered in the use of Concord",

         answer : "Gender and number",

         options : [

                          "Syntax and semantics",

                          "Subject and verb",

                          "Phrases and clauses",

                          "Gender and number"  

                          ]

    

    },

    {

         number:8,

         question: "Which is the correct expression",

         answer : "If one studies hard, one will pass",

         options : [

                          "If one studies hard, he will pass",

                          "If one studies hard, one will pass",

                          "If one studies hard, they will pass",

                          "If one studies is hard, each will pass"  

                          ]

    

    },

    {

         number:9,

         question: "Which is the correct statement",

         answer : "Either James and John or I am to blame",

         options : [

                          "Either James and John or I is to blame",

                          "Either James and John or I are to blame",

                          "Either James and John or I were to blame",

                          "Either James and John or I am to blame"  

                          ]

    

    },

    {

         number:10,

         question: "Choose the correct expression,",

         answer : "Tell me what are you discussing",

         options : [

                          "Tell me what are you discussing about",

                          "Tell me what you are discussing about",

                          "Tell me what are you discussing",

                          "Tell me what you are discussing"  

                          ]

    

    },

    {

         number:11,

         question: "Which is the correct expression",

         answer : "Jane prefers rice to beans",

         options : [

                          "Jane prefers rice than beans",

                          "Jane prefers rice to beans",

                          "Jane prefers rice over beans ",

                          "Jane prefers rice more than beans"  

                          ]

    

    },

    {

         number:12,

         question: "Which of these statements is wrongly punctuated",

         answer : "Oh my god, what a day.",

         options : [

                          "Oh my god, what a day.",

                          "Please, may I sit with you.",

                          "What is your name?",

                          "Slow, machine at work."  

                          ]

    

    }

     ];   